Bitconned is a documentary, crime film directed by Bryan Storkel.
In this true-crime documentary, three guys exploit the freewheeling cryptocurrency
market to scam millions from investors and bankroll lavish lifestyles.
Self, played by Ray Trapani.
Self, played by Robert Farkas.
Self, played by Sohrab Sharma.
Self, played by Sam Bankman-Fried.
Self, played by Damian Williams.
Bitconned is a true crime documentary film
released by Netflix on January 1, 2024.
The film was directed by Bryan Storkel.
The film follows the three founders of Centra Tech as they raised more
than $32 million in a fraudulent initial coin offering.
The documentary is being adapted by the film's producers into a podcast
series called Creating a Con: The Story Behind Bitconned.
The film explores themes of true crime, bitcoin, crypto-currencies, scathing.